good morning sir
welcome to abc bank my name is david how
may i help you
good morning naveen my name is satish
calling from bangalore
i would like to pre-close my existing
personal loan
i will surely help you in this regard
sir may i know the reason why you want
to close the loan
i don't want to pay that's trying plus
may i know your loan a quote number
please
yes please take down
one two three five six nine
sir as i can see you have the total
outstanding amount of rupees 65 000
yes that's right if you're pre-closing
the loan pre-closing charges would be
applicable
of rupees 1750.
okay shall i go ahead and take the
request for pre-closure sir
yes also please tell me when should i
pay the total amount
sure sir you will have time of seven
working days to pay the total amount of
rupees
okay please note the service request
number sir
it is two five six nine four eight five
is there any other thing that i could
assist you with no sir
okay so i am transferring this call to
ibr for your valuable feedback
thank you for calling abc bank have a
nice day
thank you naveen wish you the same
you